Grzegorz Pawlik

Senior Marketing Developer at ODIGEO

pawlik.gregor@gmail.com

Summary

I'm a full-stack developer with an emphasis on software development best practices with expertise in the following fields: - PHP (Zend, Laravel, CodeIgniter), MySQL, JavaScript (jQuery, AngularJS), HTML5, CSS3 (LESS, Sass), APIs, Git, and SVN - Modern web development techniques such as responsive web design, progressive enhancement, and ensuring concise cross-browser compatibility - Design; knowledge of UI design methodologies, significant experience with Photoshop - Working in agile development environments and as part of multidisciplinary teams

Experience

Senior Marketing Developer at eDreams ODIGEO

May 2012 - Present (3 years 8 months)

Primary Skills: PHP, JavaScript, MySQL, MongoDB, WordPress, Drupal, CodeIgniter, Zend, jQuery, AngularJS, HTML5, CSS3, LESS/Sass, JIRA, Confluence, Git, SVN, Google APIs (AdWords/Analytics/Drive), PHPUnit, Jasmine, Scrum/Kanban, Documentation, Responsive design - Development of tools and scripts to manage AdWords accounts/campaigns/adgroups/keywords at large scale via API - Responsibility for running and development of all internal social web applications and tools - Development of dynamic web components for the company assets, including twitter-like feeds, widgets and social networking metric systems - Architecture, development, and maintainance of the WordPress multi-site system - Creation of a custom CMS for Facebook and micro-site contests - Coordination across organization for project planning & process review

Full-Stack Developer at BlueBirdMedia

July 2011 - May 2012 (11 months)

Primary Skills: PHP, MySQL, JavaScript, WordPress, Drupal, Joomla, CodeIgniter, jQuery, HTML5, CSS3, Sass/Compass, Git, SVN, Bootstrap, Foundation, Facebok/Twitter API, Responsive design, Adobe Photoshop - Development of websites ranging from small business solutions to community websites receiving +10,000 unique hits a month - Development of Facebook tabs and landing pages - Management of projects from initial consultation and branding, to website launch and maintenance - Responsibility for multiple clients and coding projects every day, effective multitasking - SEO and Google Analytics analyzing of traffic, bounce rates and conversions - MySQL optimization/design for user information, e-mail lists, billing info, addresses, and website performance/statistics

Full-Stack Developer at Internet Advantage

January 2011 - August 2011 (8 months)

Primary Skills: PHP, MySQL, JavaScript, WordPress, Joomla, CodeIgniter, Sitecore, jQuery, XML, JSON, HTML, CSS, SVN, Bootstrap, Foundation, Facebok API - Front end development on multiple CMS platforms (WordPress, Joomla, Sitecore) - Comprehensive website performance and SEO optimizations - Extensive and deep cross browser debugging - Database migrations between several CMS systems - Responding to the clients' issues, offering solutions and ensuring support tickets were being taken care of on schedule

Back-End Developer at Web Koncept Studio

September 2008 - November 2009 (1 year 3 months)

Primary Skills: PHP, MySQL, JavaScript, Drupal, Joomla, jQuery, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Documentation, Adobe Photoshop - Construction, development, coding, debugging, and maintain dynamic websites using PHP - Development of HTML email marketing campaigns - Creating web layouts and banners using Photoshop - Reviewing of code and documentation of proprietary CMS - Reviewing of co-worked code

Languages

English

Spanish

German

Polish

Skills & Expertise

Web Development

PHP

HTML

CMS

jQuery

Facebook API

WordPress

HTML/XML

CSS

JavaScript

Advanced CSS

MySQL

Google Adwords

Angular.JS

Twitter API

Zend Framework

CodeIgniter

Laravel

Photoshop

MongoDB

Amazon Web Services (AWS)

Education

Wroclaw University of Technology

MSc, Telecommunication Engineering, 2004 - 2010

Universidad Miguel Hernández de Elche

Informatics and Telecommunications, 2007 - 2009